faso.com 2019-11-15

# Policies

## Privacy Policy

BoldBrush, Inc a Texas Corporation d/b/a FineArtStudioOnline ("FASO"), in Bexar County, Texas, has adopted the following Privacy Policy applicable to Personal Information that it may receive from Customers, Clients, or any other Users in connection with the services provided through this site. 

**Definitions**

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, the following definitions apply:

"Client" means a licensed user of FASO, whether such individual or company has a presence on the site.  
"Interested Customer" or "Customer" means an individual authorized to use the FASO software and FASO services to view Client sites.  
"FASO" or "We" means BoldBrush, Inc a Texas Corporation d/b/a FineArtStudioOnline.  
"Personal Information" means all personally identifiable information that we collect, receive or process with respect to use of coupons or information of Customers or Clients. Additional information about the Personal Information we collect or receive is found in the Collection and Use of Personal Information section of this Privacy Policy.  
"You" means one of the following: a FASO Client, or Interested Customer or any other individual authorized to use this site pursuant to its stated policy (collectively "User").

**Site Access**

FASO Client access to this site may be restricted by password. Interested Customer access to this site is provided to view FASO Client branded pages. Accessing this site means You agree with the License to use this site. To review the license terms please click:  

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

In providing services through this site, We may collect or receive Personal Information from You. We use Personal Information in order to provide the services to You or Your customers. We will handle and treat all Personal Information collected and received by Us through this system in the manner outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

**What Information We collect and how We use it:**

**Personal Information Collected:** The Personal Information that we collect, receive or process with respect to You through this site may include: name, address, phone number, mobile phone number, email address, log-in ID and password. We do not collect information from children. Your use of this site is Your consent for our use. Aggregation of Non-Person-Specific Data. We may statistically aggregate in non-person-specific information collected for research, to provide information, quality control, operations management, security and marketing purposes and to enhance, develop or improve our services. Transfer of Information. We may disclose Personal Information in the following situations: (a) in response to a subpoena, court order or legal process, to the extent permitted and required by law; (b) to protect the security of any Client or Customer, or the security of other persons, consistent with applicable law; (c) to address actual or suspected fraud or other illegal activities; (d) in connection with a sale, joint venture or other transfer of some or all of the assets of FASO; (e) to our contractors, third party providers, or agents, who are committed or obliged to protect the privacy of Personal Information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy. IP Address. Your IP address is used to help identify You in tracking Your visit.. The data is used in a manner that could identify You, as an individual. 

**Contact Forms:** Our site uses a contact form for patrons to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their name, address, and email address). The Customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary or for marketing, promotional or informational purposes. Customers may opt-out of receiving mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

**Links to Third Party Sites:** This site contains links to other sites. FineArtStudioOnline.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Transactions that occur between You and any third party are strictly between You and the third party and are not the responsibility of FASO. Because FASO is not responsible for the availability of these outside resources or their contents, You should direct any concerns regarding any external link to its site administrator or Webmaster. 

**Our Security and Protection of Customer Information:** This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. When You enter Your credit card information for payment for a FASO website, FASO will use a PCI compliant third party service, Braintree Payments for credit card processing. Braintree Payments offers an SSL connection and FASO will never have possession of Your credit card. If You have any questions regarding Braintree Payments policies, please review them at http://www.braintreepayments.com/ 

**FASO does not sell, trade, or rent Your personal information to others. Period.**

**Protection of Personal Information**   
We take reasonable precautions and employ reasonable security safeguards to protect Personal Information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. These precautions include physical security, administrative safeguards and encryption. Customers and Clients are responsible for safeguarding their user identification and passwords, and to change passwords periodically. In the event You become aware of a possible compromise of a password, You are responsible to change the password immediately and notify FASO. 

**Information Access and Correction**

You will have the right and obligation to keep the information on this site current and correct or to have it removed at any time. 

**Information Received from Internet Service Providers**

This website receives information that is automatically generated by a user's Internet service provider (ISP). This information may include the IP address (a number automatically assigned to a computer by the ISP), the associated URLs, domain types, the browser type used to access our site, the country, state and telephone area code, the location of the ISP's servers, the pages of our site that the user views, any search terms entered on this site, and the user's website address and email address. This information may be collected for system administration purposes, to gather broad demographic information and to monitor the level of activity on the site. FASO does not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information; however, We reserve the right to link IP addresses and other information supplied by the ISP to personally identifiable information in order to protect the integrity of our system and for security purposes. 

**Cookies**

Cookies are small text files that a website transfers to Your computer's browser. We use cookies to handle user sessions to know when a User is logged in. The cookies FASO uses may supply personally identifiable information such as Your IP address, identify Your computer, browser and Internet specifications. Our session cookies are only matched to personally identifiable information during sessions where you are logged in. 

**Transmission of Information**

Data collected and received by us in connection with the delivery of services may be transmitted to the United States, Canada and other countries. The computer servers for this site are currently based in the United States. The Internet is a global environment. By using this site and sending information to us electronically, You consent to transborder and international transmission of any Personal Information collected or processed through this site or a third party provider site. 

**Links to Other Sites**

This site may contain links to other websites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties, or by FASO. The information practices of those websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy, but by their own terms and policies, which You should read carefully. These other sites may send their cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected or processed through this site. This Privacy Policy is not intended to apply to other websites or other types of information, which may be subject to different privacy policies. 

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting an updated Privacy Policy so that You are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. We encourage You to review this Privacy Policy from time to time for any changes or updates. 

By using this Web site, You consent to the collection and use of Your information by FASO. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**

You will only receive communications from FASO if You have subscribed to our email newsletter or have requested information. Every email newsletter sent gives You the opportunity to unsubscribe with one click if You no longer wish to receive it. You can also request that FASO no longer send You information from us in the following ways: 

You can send email here, with "Opt Out" in the subject line:  

**Resolution of Concerns and Issues: How to Contact Us**

Write to us:  
Privacy and Practices  
PO Box 700534 San Antonio, TX 78270

Call us:  
877-FASO-234 

If You have difficulty in using the functionality of this system to manage data, including Personal Information, please contact us at 877-FASO-234. If You have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or how we handle Personal Information, please contact us at 844-FASO-234. We will endeavor to address Your questions and concerns. 

Effective Date: 09/01/2011
